export const data = [
    {
      id: 0,
      question: "What is a startup?",
      answer: "A startup is a young company founded by entrepreneurs to develop and bring a unique product or service to market."
    },
    {
      id: 1,
      question: "What is the role of a founder?",
      answer: "A founder is an individual who initiates and establishes a startup, often taking on multiple roles such as setting the vision, securing funding, and building a team."
    },
    {
      id: 2,
      question: "what is SpeechSynthesisUtterance in nextjs14?",
      answer: "SpeechSynthesisUtterance is a built-in web API provided by modern browsers to enable text-to-speech functionality."
    },
    {
      id: 3,
      question: "What is a business plan?",
      answer: "A business plan is a document that outlines the goals, strategies, and financial projections of a startup. It serves as a roadmap for the company's operations and growth."
    },
    {
      id: 4,
      question: "What is bootstrapping?",
      answer: "Bootstrapping is a method of self-funding a startup's growth using personal savings, revenue generated by the business, or minimal external funding."
    },
    {
      id: 5,
      question: "What is scalability in startups?",
      answer: "Scalability refers to a startup's ability to handle increased demand or growth without significant disruptions or loss in performance."
    },
    {
      id: 6,
      question: "What is the role of venture capital in startups?",
      answer: "It helps startups accelerate growth, expand operations, and bring products to market."
    },
  
    {
      id: 7,
      question: "What is a business plan?",
      answer: "A business plan is a document that outlines the goals, strategies, and financial projections of a startup. It serves as a roadmap for the company's operations and growth."
    },
    {
      id: 8,
      question: "What is bootstrapping?",
      answer: "Bootstrapping is a method of self-funding a startup's growth using personal savings, revenue generated by the business, or minimal external funding."
    },
    {
      id: 9,
      question: "What is the role of a founder?",
      answer: "A founder is an individual who initiates and establishes a startup, often taking on multiple roles such as setting the vision, securing funding, and building a team."
    },
    {
      id: 10,
      question: "What is the role of venture capital in startups?",
      answer: "It helps startups accelerate growth, expand operations, and bring products to market."
    },
  ]